

SUMMARY

Short summary: I'm a hard-working, detailoriented and responsible person.

About me: Eager to learn, make a career change and work in a field where I really enjoy what I do.

Awards & Recognition: Certified Web Developer, Codecademy Certificates of completion for HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cluj-Napoca, România +(40) 744 301-841 emanuel.caradan@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/emanuel-caradan-7b12a3228 https://github.com/cmanu07

SKILLS

Attention to Detail Self-management Punctuality HTML - 55% CSS - 55% Bootstrap - 55% JavaScript - 45% React - 40% PHP - 30%

MySQL - 40%

EMANUEL CARADAN

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

FastTrack IT - certified programming courses

Certified Graduate / November 2021 - June 2022

- Completed training for HTML, CSS and Bootstrap, JavaScript and React also in backend section PHP and MySQL
- Completed all the tasks and homework assigned.

Kruk România SRL

Financial Advisor / November 2013 - November 2021

 Managing and finding the best solutions for customers to pay their debts.

Banca Românească SA

Credit Consultant / July 2013 - November 2013

Banca Comercială Carpatica SA

Account Administrator / August 2008 - June 2013

EDUCATION

Web Development

FastTrack IT - certified programming courses Nov 2021 - Jun 2022

Finance and Banking

University "Babeş-Bolyai" - Cluj-Napoca FSEGA, 2005 - 2008

Recommendation for Emanuel CARADAN

Emanuel (a.k.a. Manu) graduated from the Web Development course I teach and I can testify he's a passionate learner, very responsible and a solution driven person. He was particularly interested in front-end development. With a keen eye for the web page design, Manu solved the projects I gave to the class, trying to make the interface as user-friendly as possible.

Also, he always tried to understand better and deeper the web development topics I presented to them. When facing a "jam", Manu was not afraid to ask for help in order to get the things done.

I would definitely recommend Manu as a web developer.

Sincerely,

Daniel FILIPAŞ, WebDev trainer

June 10, 2022